<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC "-//APACHE//DTD Documentation V2.0//EN" "http://forrest.apache.org/dtd/document-v20.dtd">
<document>
	<header>
		<title>jcgm -- Version history</title>
	</header>
	<body>
		<section id="core">
			<title>
				Core Package
			</title>
			<section id="core-trunk">
				<title>Development Branch (Trunk)</title>
				<p>
					Changes in the latest development version:
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li></li>
				</ul>
			</section>
			<section id="core-0.2.0">
				<title>Version 0.2.0</title>
				<p>
					Changes in the core library:
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>added another split method with an extractor that accepts input streams</li>
					<li>added CgmException class</li>
					<li>fixed an issue with background colors</li>
					<li>added support for BeginTileArray, BitonalTile (partial), DeviceViewportSpecificationMode, EndTileArray, NamePrecision, Tile (partial)</li>
					<li>added a method to be able to read structured data records</li>
					<li>support for transparent CGM files was added. Use <code>CGMDisplay.setTransparent(true)</code>, thanks clivebutler</li>
					<li>added patch by clivebutler to only have images with zero dimension when the extent is empty</li>
					<li>fixed a problem for cell arrays using color selection mode "indexed" and representation flag "packed list"</li>
					<li>integrated patch from tmyroadctfig: added support for
						APPLICATION DATA and MESSAGE commands; made command
						classes public</li>
					<li>only clear the view once for multiple picture images (workaround only)</li>
					<li>corrected a problem with font sizes on images with small
					extents</li>
				</ul>
			</section>
			<section id="core-0.1.1">
				<title>Version 0.1.1</title>
				<p>
					Changes in the core library:
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed a problem with Metafile Defaults Replacement that didn't support long form commands.</li>
					<li>Fixed a problem with Circular Arc Centre, Polygon and Polyline which didn't respect the parameter precision correctly.</li>
					<li>The Text and Restricted Text commands are now using common code</li>
					<li>Fixed a problem with scaling for the Text element (rev. 21)</li>
					<li>New method <code>CGM.split</code> to split CGM files containing several CGM files into pieces</li>
				</ul>
				<p>
					Other changes
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>New viewer application in the examples to view and compare CGM files to a reference image</li>
				</ul>
			</section>
			<section id="core-0.1.0">
				<title>Version 0.1.0</title>
				<p>
					Initial version.
				</p>
			</section>
		</section>
		<section id="image">
			<title>
				Image Package
			</title>
			<section id="image-trunk">
				<title>Development Branch (Trunk)</title>
				<p>
					Changes in the latest development version:
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>The <code>ImageReadParam.setSourceTenderSize(Dimension)</code> method can now be used to define the size of the rendered CGM image, thanks clivebutler.</li>
				</ul>
			</section>
			<section id="image-0.1.1">
				<title>Version 0.1.1</title>
				<ul>
					<li>The <code>CGMImageReaderSpi</code> now correctly checks
						for the BEGIN METAFILE command and ignores the
						parameter length, this prevented some CGM files to be
						recognized correctly</li>
				</ul>
			</section>
			<section id="image-0.1.0">
				<title>Version 0.1.0</title>
				<p>
					Initial version.
				</p>
			</section>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
